{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Wise",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1914",
    "human_readable": "Robert Wise was born in 1914.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8757640719413757,
            "question": "In what year was Robert Wise born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.591815710067749,
            "question": "What was Robert Wise's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46216198801994324,
            "question": "What is Robert Wise known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3197909891605377,
            "question": "Who were some notable collaborators with Robert Wise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2750394344329834,
            "question": "Was Robert Wise an actor, director, or both?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16797146201133728,
            "question": "Was Robert Wise involved in any other areas of filmmaking besides directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14719508588314056,
            "question": "Did Robert Wise win any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14224082231521606,
            "question": "Name some of the films directed by Robert Wise."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13765671849250793,
            "question": "How long was Robert Wise active in the film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10714884102344513,
            "question": "What genre of films did Robert Wise often work in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Wise was born in 1914.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5603_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How long was Robert Wise active in the film industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5603_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name some of the films directed by Robert Wise.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5603_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Robert Wise win any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5603_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5603_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5603_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5603_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5603_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5603_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5603_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5603_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5603_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5603_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5603_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Robert Wise was born on September 10, 1914 (or September 19, 1914, but one document is incorrect) which means he was indeed born in 1914."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in the documents, which state that Robert Wise was indeed born on September 10, 1914."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}